<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM
    "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
    <entry key="joke0">Three guys, stranded on a desert island, find a magic lantern containing a
        genie, who grants them each one wish. The first guy wishes he was off the island and back
        home. The second guy wishes the same. The third guy says "I’m lonely. I wish my friends were
        back here."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke1">A newlywed couple moves into their new house. One day the husband comes home
        from work and his wife says, "Honey, you know, in the upstairs bathroom one of the pipes is
        leaking, could you fix it?" The husband says, "What do I look like, Mr. Plumber?" A few days
        go by, and he comes home from work and his wife says, "Honey, the car won't start. I think
        it needs a new battery. Could you change it for me?" He says: "What do I look like, Mr.
        Goodwrench?" Another few days go by, and it's raining pretty hard. The wife finds a leak in
        the roof. She says, "Honey, there's a leak on the roof! Can you please fix it?" He says,
        "What do I look like, Bob Vila?" The next day the husband comes home, and the roof is fixed.
        So is the plumbing. So is the car. He asks his wife what happened. "Oh, I had a handyman
        come in and fix them," she says. "Great! How much is that going to cost me?" he snarls. Wife
        says: "Nothing. He said he'd do it for free if I either baked him a cake or slept with him."
        "Uh, well, what kind of cake did you make?" asks the husband. "What do I look like," she
        says, "Betty Crocker?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke2">A young boy enters a barber shop and the barber whispers to his customer,
        “This is the dumbest kid in the world. Watch while I prove it to you.” The barber puts a
        dollar bill in one hand and two quarters in the other, then calls the boy over and asks,
        “Which do you want, son?” The boy takes the quarters and leaves. “What did I tell you?” said
        the barber. “That kid never learns!” Later, when the customer leaves, he sees the same young
        boy coming out of the ice cream store. “Hey, son! May I ask you a question? Why did you take
        the quarters instead of the dollar bill?” The boy licked his cone and replied, “Because the
        day I take the dollar, the game is over!”
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke3">It's Game 7 of the Stanley Cup Final, and a man makes his way to his seat
        right at center ice. He sits down, noticing that the seat next to him is empty. He leans
        over and asks his neighbor if someone will be sitting there. "No" says the neighbor. "The
        seat is empty." "This is incredible," said the man. "Who in their right mind would have a
        seat like this for the Stanley Cup and not use it?" The neighbor says, "Well, actually, the
        seat belongs to me. I was supposed to come with my wife, but she passed away. This is the
        first Stanley Cup we haven't been to together since we got married." "Oh, I'm so sorry to
        hear that. That's terrible... But couldn't you find someone else, a friend or relative, or
        even a neighbor to take the seat?" The man shakes his head. "No,” he says. “They're all at
        the funeral."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke4">A guy has a talking dog. He brings it to a talent scout. "This dog can speak
        English," he claims to the unimpressed agent. "Okay, Sport," the guys says to the dog,
        "what’s on the top of a house?" "Roof!" the dog replies. "Oh, come on..." the talent agent
        responds. "All dogs go ‘roof’." "No, wait," the guy says. He asks the dog "what does
        sandpaper feel like?" "Rough!" the dog answers. The talent agent gives a condescending blank
        stare. He is losing his patience. "No, hang on," the guy says. "This one will amaze you. "
        He turns and asks the dog: "Who, in your opinion, was the greatest baseball player of all
        time?" "Ruth!" goes the dog. And the talent scout, having seen enough, boots them out of his
        office onto the street. And the dog turns to the guy and says "Maybe I shoulda said
        DiMaggio?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke5">Two campers are hiking in the woods when one is bitten on the rear end by a
        rattlesnake. "I’ll go into town for a doctor," the other says. He runs ten miles to a small
        town and finds the town’s only doctor, who is delivering a baby. "I can’t leave," the doctor
        says. ‘But here’s what to do. Take a knife, cut a little X where the bite is, suck out the
        poison and spit it on the ground." The guy ruins back to his friend, who is in agony. ‘What
        did the doctor say?" the victim asks. "He says you’re gonna die."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke6">On a passenger flight, the pilot comes over the public address system as
        usual and to greet the passengers. He tells them at what altitude they’ll be flying, the
        expected arrival time, and a bit about the weather, and advises them to relax and have a
        good flight.. Then, forgetting to turn off the microphone, he says to his co-pilot, "What
        would relax me right now is a cup of coffee and a blowjob." All the passengers hear it. As a
        stewardess immediately begins to run toward the cockpit to tell the pilot of his slip-up,
        one of the passengers stops her and says "Don’t forget the coffee!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke7">A guy meets a hooker in a bar. She says, "This is your lucky night. I’ve got
        a special game for you. I’ll do absolutely anything you want for $300, as long as you can
        say it in three words." The guy replies, "Hey, why not?" He pull his wallet out of his
        pocket, and one at a time lays three hundred-dollar bills on the bar, and says, slowly:
        "Paint…my…house."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke8">A guy is sitting at home when he hears a knock at the door. He opens the door
        and sees a snail on the porch. He picks up the snail and throws it as far as he can. Three
        years later, there’s a knock on the door. He opens it and sees the same snail. The snail
        says "What the hell was that all about?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke9">Three kids come down to the kitchen and sit around the breakfast table. The
        mother asks the oldest boy what he’d like to eat. "I’ll have some fuckin’ French toast," he
        says. The mother is outraged at his language, hits him, and sends him upstairs. She asks the
        middle child what he wants. "Well, I guess that leaves more fuckin’ French toast for me," he
        says. She is livid, smacks him, and sends him away. Finally she asks the youngest son what
        he wants for breakfast. "I don’t know," he says meekly, "but I definitely don’t want the
        fuckin’ French toast."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke10">A guy enters a bar carrying an alligator. Says to the patrons, "Here’s a
        deal. I'll open this alligator's mouth and place my genitals inside. The gator will close
        his mouth for one minute, then open it, and I'll remove my unit unscathed. If it works,
        everyone buys me drinks." The crowd agrees. The guy drops his pants and puts his privates in
        the gator's mouth. Gator closes mouth. After a minute, the guy grabs a beer bottle and bangs
        the gator on the top of its head. The gator opens wide, and he removes his genitals
        unscathed. Everyone buys him drinks. Then he says: "I'll pay anyone $100 who's willing to
        give it a try." After a while, a hand goes up in the back of the bar. It's a woman. "I'll
        give it a try," she says, "but you have to promise not to hit me on the head with the beer
        bottle."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke11">Two campers are walking through the woods when a huge brown bear suddenly
        appears in the clearing about 50 feet in front of them. The bear sees the campers and begins
        to head toward them. The first guys drops his backpack, digs out a pair of sneakers, and
        frantically begins to put them on. The second guys says, "What are you doing? Sneakers won’t
        help you outrun that bear." "I don't need to outrun the bear," the first guy says. "I just
        need to outrun you."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke12">My grandfather always said, "Don't watch your money; watch your health." So
        one day while I was watching my health, someone stole my money. It was my grandfather.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke13">A guy dies and is sent to Hell. Satan meets him, shows him doors to three
        rooms, and says he must choose one to spend eternity in. In the first room, people are
        standing in shit up to their necks. The guy says "no, let me see the next room." In the
        second room, people are standing with shit up to their noses. Guy says no again. Finally,
        Satan opens the door to the third room. People are standing with shit up to their knees,
        drinking coffee and eating danish pastries. The guy says, "I pick this room." Satan says
        okay and starts to leave, and the guy wades in and starts pouring some coffee. On the way
        out Satan yells, "O.K., coffee break's over. Everyone back on your heads!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke14">A guy joins a monastery and takes a vow of silence: he’s allowed to say two
        words every seven years. After the first seven years, the elders bring him in and ask for
        his two words. "Cold floors," he says. They nod and send him away. Seven more years pass.
        They bring him back in and ask for his two words. He clears his throats and says, "Bad
        food." They nod and send him away. Seven more years pass. They bring him in for his two
        words. "I quit," he says. "That’s not surprising," the elders say. "You’ve done nothing but
        complain since you got here."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke15">I was walking across a bridge one day, and I saw a man standing on the edge,
        about to jump off. So I ran over and said "Stop! Don't do it!" "Why shouldn't I?" he said.
        "Well, there's so much to live for!" "Like what?" "Well... are you religious?" He said yes.
        I said, "Me too! Are you Christian or Buddhist?" "Christian." "Me too! Are you Catholic or
        Protestant ? "Protestant." "Me too! Are you Episcopalian or Baptist?" "Baptist" "Wow! Me
        too! Are you Baptist Church of God or Baptist Church of the Lord?" "Baptist Church of God!"
        "Me too! Are you original Baptist Church of God, or are you reformed Baptist Church of God?"
        "Reformed Baptist Church of God!" "Me too! Are you Reformed Baptist Church of God,
        reformation of 1879, or Reformed Baptist Church of God, reformation of 1915?" He said,
        "Reformed Baptist Church of God, reformation of 1915!" I said, "Die, heretic scum", and
        pushed him off.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke16">Two guys are walking down the street when a mugger approaches them and
        demands their money. They both grudgingly pull out their wallets and begin taking out their
        cash. Just then one guy turns to the other and hands him a bill. "Here’s that $20 I owe
        you," he says.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke17">I went to the psychiatrist, and he says "You're crazy." I tell him I want a
        second opinion. He says, "Okay, you're ugly too!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke18">Saul is working in his store when he hears a booming voice from above:
        "Saul, sell your business." He ignores it. It goes on for days. "Saul, sell your business
        for $3 million." After weeks of this, he relents, sells his store. The voice says ‘Saul, go
        to Las Vegas." He asks why. "Saul, take the $3 million to Las Vegas." He obeys, goes to a
        casino. Voice says, "Saul , go to the blackjack table and put it down all on one hand." He
        hesitates but knows he must. He’s dealt an 18. The dealer has a six showing. "Saul, take a
        card." What? The dealer has -- "Take a card!" He tells the dealer to hit him. Saul gets an
        ace. Nineteen. He breathes easy. "Saul, take another card." What? "TAKE ANOTHER CARD!" He
        asks for another card. It’s another ace. He has twenty. "Saul, take another card," the voice
        commands. I have twenty! Saul shouts. "TAKE ANOTHER CARD!!" booms the voice. Hit me,Saul
        says. He gets another ace. Twenty one. The booming voice goes: "un-fucking-believable!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke19">A Jewish grandmother is watching her grandchild playing on the beach when a
        huge wave comes and takes him out to sea. She pleads, "please God, save my only grandson. I
        beg of you, bring him back." And a big wave comes and washes the boy back onto the beach,
        good as new. She looks up to heaven and says: "He had a hat!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke20">I always look for a woman who has a tattoo. I see a woman with a tattoo, and
        I’m thinking, okay, here’s a gal who’s capable of making a decision she’ll regret in the
        future.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke21">A Jewish man is walking on the beach when he discovers a bottle containing
        genie. He rubs it and a genie comes out, promises to grant him one wish. He says, "Peace in
        the Middle east, that's my wish." The genie looks concerned, then says "No, I'm sorry,
        that's just not possible. Some things just can't be changed. Do you have another wish?" The
        guys says 'Well...for my whole life I've never receievd oral sex from my wife. That would be
        my wish." The genie pauses for another moment and then says "How would you define peace?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke22">Two Irish guys are fishing. The first guy reels in his line and sees that
        he's snagged an old bottle. As he's taking it off the hook, a genie pops out and promises to
        grant him one wish. "Turn the lake into beer," he says. The genie goes "Poof!" and the lake
        turns into beer. He says to the other guy, "So what do you think?" The other guy says, "You
        jerk. Now we've got to piss in the boat."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke23">I was on the subway, sitting on a newspaper, and a guy comes over and asks
        "Are you reading that?" I didn’t know what to say. So I said yes. I stood up, turned the
        page, and sat down again.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke24">A guy shows up late for work. The boss yells "You should have been here at
        8:30!" he replies: "Why? What happened at 8:30?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke25">They say animal behavior can warn you when an earthquake is coming. Like the
        night before that last earthquake hit, our family dog took the car keys and drove to
        Arizona.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke26">I have a large seashell collection, which I keep scattered on beaches all
        over the world.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke27">I can’t think of anything worse after a night of drinking than waking up
        next to someone and not being able to remember their name, or how you met, or why they’re
        dead.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke28">Last night I went to a 24-hour grocery. When I got there, the guy was
        locking the front door. I said, "Hey, the sign says you're open 24 hours." He goes: "Not in
        a row!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke29">Jesus and Saint Peter are golfing. St. Peter steps up to the tee on a par
        three and hits one long and straight. It reaches the green. Jesus is up next. He slices it.
        It heads over the fence into traffic on an adjacent street. Bounces off a truck, onto the
        roof of a nearby shack and into the rain gutter, down the drain spout and onto a lilly pad
        at the edge of a lake. A frog jumps up and snatches the ball in his mouth. An eagle swoops
        down, grabs the frog. As the eagle flies over the green, the frog croaks and drops the ball.
        It’s in the hole. Saint Peter looks at Jesus, exasperated. "Are you gonna play golf?" he
        asks "Or are you just gonna fuck around?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke30">TV commercials now show you how detergents take out bloodstains, a pretty
        violent image there. I think if you've got a T-shirt with a bloodstain all over it, maybe
        laundry isn't your biggest problem.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke31">China has a population of a billion people. One billion. That means even if
        you’re a one in a million kind of guy, there are still a thousand others exactly like you.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke32">A Jewish guy goes into a confession box. "Father O’Malley," he says, "my
        name is Emil Cohen. I’m seventy eight years old. Believe it or not, I’m currently involved
        with a 28 year old girl, and also, on the side, her 19 year old sister. We engage in all
        manner of pleasure, and in my entire life I’ve never felt better." "My good man," says the
        priest, "I think you’ve come to the wrong place. Why are you telling me?" And the guy goes:
        "I’m telling everybody!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke33">A father is explaining ethics to his son, who is about to go into business.
        "Suppose a woman comes in and orders a hundred dollars worth of material. You wrap it up,
        and you give it to her. She pays you with a $100 bill. But as she goes out the door you
        realize she’s given you two $100 bills. Now, here’s where the ethics come in: should you or
        should you not tell your partner?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke34">A guy tells his psychiatrist: ‘It was terrible. I was away on business, and
        I emailed my wife that I’d be back a day early. I rushed home from the airport and found her
        in bed with my best friend. I don’t get it. How could she do this to me?" "Well," says the
        psychiatrist. "Maybe she didn’t see the email."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke35">My sister was with two men in one night. She could hardly walk after that.
        Can you imagine? Two dinners!
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke36">Sid and Irv are business partners. They make a deal that whichever one dies
        first will contact the living one from the afterlife. So Irv dies. Sid doesn't hear from him
        for about a year, figures there is no afterlife. Then one day he gets a call. It's Irv. "So
        there is an afterlife! What's it like?" Sid asks. 'Well, I sleep very late. I get up, have a
        big breakfast. Then I have sex, lots of sex. Then I go back sleep, but I get up for lunch,
        have a big lunch. Have some more sex. Take a nap. Huge dinner. More sex. Go to sleep, and
        wake up the next day." "Oh, my god," says Sid "So that's what heaven is like?" "Oh no," says
        Irv. "I'm not in heaven. I'm a bear in Yellowstone Park."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke37">I was coming back from Canada, driving through Customs, and the guy asked,
        "Do you have any firearms with you?" I said: "What do you need?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke38">Jack Benny is walking down the street, when a stick-up man pulls out a gun
        and says "Your money or your life!" An extremely long silence follows. "Your money or your
        life!" the thug repeats. Finally Benny says "I’m thinking!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke39">My wife and I took out life insurance policies on each other -- so now it's
        just a waiting game.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke40">Last time I was down South, I was in a restaurant and ordered some chicken,
        and these three cousins, you know the ones I mean, Klu, Kluck and Klan, come up and say
        "Boy, we’re givin’ you fair warnin’. Anything you do to that chicken, we’re gonna do to
        you." So I put down my knife and fork, and I picked up that chicken, and I kissed it.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke41">A lady at a party goes up to Winston Churchill and tells him, "Sir, you are
        drunk." Churchill replies, "Madam, you are ugly. In the morning, I shall be sober."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke42">I failed my driver’s test. The guy asked me "what do you do at a red light?"
        I said, I don’t know… look around, listen to the radio…
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke43">I celebrated Thanksgiving in an old-fashioned way. I invited everyone in my
        neighborhood to my house, we had an enormous feast, and then I killed them and took their
        land.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke44">I feel sorry for people who don’t drink or do drugs. Because someday they’re
        going to be in a hospital bed, dying, and they won’t know why.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke45">I was so ugly when I was born, the doctor slapped my mother.</entry>
    <entry key="joke46">At a White House party, a woman approached Calvin Coolidge, famed for his
        silence, and said "Mr. President, I made a bet I can get more than two words out of you." He
        replied: "You lose."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke47">I bought a box of animal crackers and it said on it "Do not eat if seal is
        broken." So I opened up the box, and sure enough...
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke48">I know a guy who called up the Home Shopping Network. They said "Can I help
        you?" and he said "No, I'm just looking."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke49">A guy asks a lawyer what his fee is. "I charge $50 for three questions," the
        lawyer says. "That’s awfully steep, isn’t it?" the guy asks. "Yes," the lawyer replies, "Now
        what’s your final question?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke50">I bet the main reason the police keep people away from a plane crash is they
        don’t want anybody walking in and lying down in the crash stuff, then, when somebody comes
        up, act like they just woke up and go, "What was that?!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke51">After 12 years of therapy my psychiatrist said something that brought tears
        to my eyes.. He said, "No hablo ingles."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke52">An old woman is upset at her husband’s funeral. "You have him in a brown
        suit and I wanted him in a blue suit" The mortician says "We’ll take care of it, ma’am" and
        yells back, "Ed, switch the heads on two and four!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke53">Stuffed deer heads on walls are bad enough, but it’s worse when you see them
        wearing dark glasses, having streamers around their necks and a hat on their antlers.
        Because then you know they were enjoying themselves at a party when they were shot.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke54">I went to a fight the other night and a hockey game broke out.</entry>
    <entry key="joke55">A Catholic teenager goes to confession, and after confessing to an affair
        with a girl is told by the priest that he can't be forgiven unless he reveals who the girl
        is. "I promised not to tell!" he says. "Was it Mary Patricia, the butcher's daughter?" the
        preist asks. "No, and I said I wouldn't tell." "Was it Mary Elizabeth, the printer's
        daughter?" "No, and I still won't tell!" 'Was it Mary Francis, the baker's daughter?" "No,"
        says the boy. 'Well, son," says the priest, "I have no choice but to excommunicate you for
        six months." Outside, the boy's friends ask what happened. "Well," he says, "I got six
        months, but three good leads."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke56">A man is driving his five year old to a friend’s house when another car
        races in front and cuts them off, nearly causing an accident. "Douchebag!" the father yells.
        A moment later he realizes the indiscretion, pulls over, and turns to face his son. "Your
        father just said a bad word," he says. "I was angry at that driver, but that was no excuse
        for what I said. It was wrong. But just because I said it, it doesn’t make it right, and I
        don’t ever want to hear you saying it. Is that clear?" His son looks at him and says: "Too
        late, douchebag."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke57">There’s always one of my uncles who watches a boxing match with me and says
        "Sure. Ten million dollars. You know, for that kind of money, I’d fight him." As if someone
        is going to pay $200 a ticket to see a 57-year-old carpet salesman get hit in the face once
        and cry.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke58">I went to a restaurant with a sign that said they served breakfast at any
        time. So I ordered French toast during the Renaissance.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke59">I was making love to this girl and she started crying. I said, "Are you
        going to hate yourself in the morning?" She said. "No. I hate myself now."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke60">When I went to college, my parents threw a going away party for me,
        according to the letter.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke61">I knew these Siamese twins. They moved to England, so the other one could
        drive.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke62">A lawyer dies and goes to Heaven. "There must be some mistake," the lawyer
        argues. "I’m too young to die. I’m only fifty five." "Fifty five?" says Saint Peter. "No,
        according to out calculations, you’re eighty two." "How’s you get that?" the lawyer asks.
        Answers St. Peter: "We added up your time sheets."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke63">The only thing I know about Africa is that it's far, far away. About a
        thirty-five hour flight. The boat ride's so long, there are still slaves on their way here.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke64">A man goes to a psychiatrist and says, "Doc, my brother's crazy, he thinks
        he's a chicken." The doctor says, "Why don't you turn him in?" The guy says, "We would. But
        we need the eggs."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke65">The guy who shot Robert Kennedy, Sirhan Sirhan, goes up for parole every
        year. Once he even told the parole board that if Kennedy was alive today, he would speak in
        his favor and say let him go. What a tough break, you know? The one guy who would have
        supported him, and he shot him.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke66">Two snowmen are standing in a meadow. One snowman turns to the other and
        says, "Do you smell carrots?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke67">I would never want to belong to any club that would have someone like me for
        member.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke68">A guy with a huge orange head goes in to see a doctor. The doctor says, "How
        did you get such a huge orange head?" The guy says, "Well, one day I was walking down the
        beach when I tripped over an old lantern. A genie came out and said, I'll grant you three
        wishes, whatever you desire...what is your first wish?' I said, I'd like all the money I
        could ever spend.' The genie went Poof!', and there it was, all the money I could ever
        spend. Then he said, What is your second wish?' I said, I'd like a beautiful woman to love
        me, someone I could enjoy this money with.' The genie went Poof!', and there she was, a
        gorgeous girl who immediately loved me. Then the genie said, And what is your third
        wish?'...and I think this is where I went wrong...I said, I'd like a huge orange head.'"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke69">If this is coffee, please bring me some tea. If this is tea, please bring me
        some coffee.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke70">I went to my doctor and told him "my penis is burning." He said, "That means
        somebody is talking about it."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke71">Sincerity is everything. If you can fake that, you’ve got it made.</entry>
    <entry key="joke72">I was born a suspect. I can walk down any street in America and women will
        clutch their purses tighter, hold onto their Mace, lock their car doors. If I look up into
        the windows of the apartments I pass I can see old ladies on the phone. They’ve already
        dialed 9-1- and are just waiting for me to do something wrong.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke73">Last night, it was so cold, the flashers in New York were only describing
        themselves.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke74">New York now leads the world's great cities in the number of people around
        whom you shouldn't make a sudden move.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke75">Mario Andretti has retired from race car driving. That's a good thing. He's
        getting old. He ran his entire last race with his left blinker on.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke76">At the airport they asked me if anybody I didn’t know gave me anything. Even
        the people I know don’t give me anything.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke77">I want to have children, but my friends scare me. One of my friends told me
        she was in labor for thirty six hours. I don’t even want to do anything that feels good for
        thirty-six hours.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke78">Three comedians are shooting the breeze at the back of a nightclub after a
        late gig. They’ve heard one another’s material so much, they’ve reached the point where they
        don’t need to say the jokes anymore to amuse each other – they just need to refer to each
        joke by a number. "Number 37!" cracks the first comic, and the others break up. ""Number
        53!" says the second guy, and they howl. Finally, it’s the third comic’s turn. "44!" he
        quips. He gets nothing. Crickets. "What?" he asks, "Isn’t 44 funny?" "Sure, it’s usually
        hilarious," they answer. "But the way you tell it…"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke79">Two ministers doing missionary work in the South Seas are captured by a
        tribe and tied to stakes. The chief says to them, "You have a choice – death, or ugga
        bugga." The first guy says, "Well, I guess ugga bugga." The chief shouts "UGGA BUGGA!" and
        30 members of the tribe attack and sodomize the first missionary. The chief then asks the
        second minister, "Now you have a choice, death or ugga bugga." He says "well, my religion
        does not allow me to choose ugga bugga, so I suppose it must be death." The chief says,
        "Very well," and shouts "DEATH. But first, UGGA BUGGA!
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke80">My grandfather is hard of hearing. He needs to read lips. I don’t mind him
        reading lips, but he uses one of those yellow highlighters.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke81">A guy has a parrot that can sing and speak beautifully. He takes it to the
        synagogue on Rosh Hashonah and makes a wager that the bird can conduct the High Holiday
        service better than the temple’s cantor. When the big moment comes, though, the parrot is
        silent. The guy is outraged. He takes the bird home and is about to kill it when the bird
        finally speaks: "Schmuck! Think of the odds we’ll get on Yom Kippur!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke82">I always keep a supply of stimulant handy in case I see a snake, which I
        also keep handy.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke83">A car hits a Jewish man. The paramedic rushes over and says, "Are you
        comfortable?" The guy says: "I make a good living."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke84">A comedian is sitting at the bar of a comedy club late one night when a
        beautiuful woman comes up to him and says "I saw you perform tonight, and you’re the
        funniest guy I’ve ever seen. I want to take you home and give you the hottest night of sex
        you’re ever had." The comedian looks at her and says, "Did you see the first show or the
        second show?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke85">Waiters and waitresses are becoming nicer and much more caring. I used to
        pay my check, they'd say "Thank you." That graduated into "Have a nice day." That’s now
        escalated into "You care care of yourself, now." The other day I paid my check – the waiter
        said, "Don’t put off that mammogram."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke86">I worked some gigs in the Deep South…Alabama…You talk about Darwin’s waiting
        room. There are guys in Alabama who are their own father.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke87">We had a depression fair in the back yard. A major game there was Pin the
        Blame on the Donkey.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke88">Animals may be our friends. But they won’t pick you up at the airport.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke89">I was thrown out of NYU. On my metaphysics final, they caught me cheating. I
        looked within the soul of the boy sitting next to me.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke90">Last night I was having dinner with Charles Manson, and in the middle of
        dinner he turned to me and said "Is it hot in here, or am I crazy?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke91">Last year, I deducted 10,697 cartons of cigarettes as a business expense.
        The tax man said, "Don’t ever let us catch you without a cigarette in your hand."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke92">If I ever have twins, I'd use one for parts.</entry>
    <entry key="joke93">Two old actors are sitting on a bench. One says: "How long has it been since
        you had a job?" The other actor says "Thirty two years -- how about you?" The first actor
        says, "That's nothing. I haven't had a job in forty years!" The other says, "One of these
        days we've got to get out of this business!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke94">Two old ladies are in a restaurant. One complains, "You know, the food here
        is just terrible." The other shakes her head and adds, "And such small portions."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke95">I had a cab driver in Paris. The man smelled like a guy eating cheese while
        getting a permanent inside the septic tank of a slaughterhouse.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke96">Contrary to what most people would say, the most dangerous animal in the
        world is not the lion or the tiger or even the elephant. It’s a shark riding on an
        elephant’s back, just trampling and eating everything they see.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke97">In football you wear a helmet; in baseball you wear a cap. Football is
        concerned with downs; baseball is concerned with ups. In football you receive a penalty; in
        baseball you make an error. In football the specialist comes in to kick; in baseball the
        specialist comes in to relieve somebody.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke98">Take my wife…please</entry>
    <entry key="joke99">L.A. is so celebrity-conscious, there's a restaurant that only serves Jack
        Nicholson -- and when he shows up, they tell him there'll be a ten-minute wait.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke100">I believe Dr. Kevorkian is onto something. I think he’s great. Because
        suicide is our way of saying to God, "You can’t fire me. I quit."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke101">
        Old guy dies, wife phones Jewish Chronicle to place an obituary, is
        told that there is a minimum charge which is for six words.

        Obituary appears: Samuel Goldstein deceased, Volvo for sale.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke102">
        All men are born equal, but quite a few eventually get over it....

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke103">
        Q: How many bricks did it take to finish building the
        National Cathedral?

        A: One....it only takes one brick to finish a building.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke104">
        A little girl named Sally loved animal crackers. Her mom took her to
        the store and bought her some. When they got home, Sally started
        taking out all the animal crackers from the box and laid them all out
        on the table. Her mother asked why she was doing that. Sally replied,
        "I'm looking for the seal. The box says if the seal is broken, don't
        eat it."

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke105">
        Exchange between a defense attorney and a farmer with a bodily injury
        claim. It came from a Houston, Texas insurance agent.

        Attorney: "At the scene of the accident, did you tell the constable
        you had never felt better in your life?"

        Farmer: "That's right."

        Attorney: "Well, then, how is it that you are now claiming you were
        seriously injured when my client's auto hit your wagon?"

        Farmer: "When the constable arrived, he went over to my horse, who had
        a broken leg, and shot him. Then he went over to Rover, my dog, who
        was all banged up, and shot him. When he asked me how I felt, I just
        thought under the circumstances, it was a wise choice of words to say
        I've never felt better in my life.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke106">
        Two carrots were walking down the road when a huge transfer truck
        slammed into one of them. An ambulance was called and they rushed the
        little fellow off to the hospital where he immediately went into
        hours of surgery. Finally the doctor emerged and approached the other
        carrot who had been anxiously awaiting in the waiting room. "Tell me
        Doc, how is he?"

        The doctor replied, "I've got some good news and some bad news. The
        good news is he's going to live. The bad news is we're pretty sure
        he's going to be a vegetable for the rest of his life.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke107">
        If people don't like tailgaters, why do they buy bumper stickers?

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke108">
        A small boy is sent to bed by his father. Five minutes later:
        "Da-ad..." "What?" "I'm thirsty. Can you bring me a drink of water?"
        "No. You had your chance. Lights out."

        Five minutes later: "Da-aaaad..." "WHAT?" "I'm THIRSTY...Can I have a
        drink of water??" "I told you NO! If you ask again I'll have to spank
        you!!"

        Five minutes later... "Daaaa-aaaad..." "WHAT??!!"
        "When you come in to spank me, can you bring me a drink of water?"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke109">
        A man in a bar sees a friend at a table, drinking by himself.
        Approaching the friend he comments, "You look terrible. What's the
        problem?"

        "My mother died in June," he said, "and left me $10,000."

        "Gee, that's tough," he replied.

        "Then in July," the friend continued, "My father died, leaving me
        $50,000."

        "Wow. Two parents gone in two months. No wonder you're depressed."

        "And last month my aunt died, and left me $15,000."

        "Three close family members lost in three months? How sad."

        "Then this month," continued, the friend, "nothing!"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke110">
        Q: How many feminists does it take to change a lightbulb?

        A: It's society that needs changing!! Not the lightbulb!!!

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke111">
        Truly Stupid Sports Quotes

        "I know the Virginia players are smart because you need a 1500
        SAT to get in. I have to drop bread crumbs to get our players to
        and from class"
        - George Raveling [when he was at Washington State, not USC,
        but I imagine that the problem got worse], basketball coach

        "You guys pair up in groups of three, then line up in a circle"
        - Bill Peterson, a Florida State football coach

        "You guys line up alphabetically by height"
        - Bill Peterson, a Florida State football coach

        "I play football. I'm not trying to be a professor. The tests don't
        seem to make sense to me, measuring your brain on stuff I haven't
        been through in school."
        -Clemson recruit Ray Forsythe, who was ineligible as a freshman
        because of academic requirements

        "Why would anyone expect him to come out smarter? He went to
        prison for three years, not Princeton."
        -Boxing promoter Dan Duva on Mike Tyson hooking up again with
        promoter Don King

        "That's so when I forget how to spell my name, I can still find my
        #%@# clothes."
        -Stu Grimson, Chicago Blackhawks left wing, explaining why he
        keeps a color photo of himself above his locker

        "I can't really remember the names of the clubs that we went to."
        -Shaquille O'Neal on whether he had visited the Parthenon
        during his visit to Greece

        "I'm going to graduate on time, no matter how long it takes."
        -Senior basketball player at the University of Pittsburgh

        "Nobody in football should be called a genius. A genius is a guy
        like Norman Einstein."
        -Football commentator and former player Joe Theismann >>>>>

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke112">
        Did you know that scientists have found the one thing that can replace
        the work that ten men can do?

        A woman.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke113">
        A government who robs Peter to pay Paul can always depend on the
        support of Paul.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke114">
        They have now found proof that there were automobiles in the times of
        Adam and Eve.......

        And it is said "God drove Adam and Eve from the Garden of Eden in his
        Fury"

        And the Twelve Apostles were very, very uncomfortable wherever they
        went -- because they were "all in one Accord."

        Don't forget that the Triumph of David roared throughout the whole
        land.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke115">
        In 1965 lawyer Andre Francois Raffray agreed to ``purchase'' the house
        of an elderly client at the then steep price of $500-a-month
        installments---on condition that he would inherit the property
        outright the moment she died. Last week, 30 years older and $180,000
        poorer, Raffray, 77, expired on Christmas Day. His client, Jeanne
        Calment, celebrated the holiday with a sumptuous hotel banquet in her
        home town of Arles. ``We all make bad deals in life,'' she joked to
        Raffray when she turned 120 early last year. She is officially the
        oldest person in the world. (Time, 8 Jan, 1996, p. 8)

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke116">
        If at first you don't succeed, skydiving isn't for you.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke117">
        Labor or Hard Labor.....you decide!

        In prison you spend the majority of your time in an 8'x10 cell.
        At work you spend most of your time in a 6'x8'cubicle.

        In prison you get three meals a day.
        At work you only get a break for one meal and you have to pay for it.

        In prison you get time off for good behavior.
        At work you get rewarded for good behavior with more work.

        In prison a guard locks and unlocks all the doors for you.
        At work you must carry around a security card and unlock and open all
        the doors yourself.

        In prison you can watch TV and play games.
        At work you get fired for watching TV and playing games.

        In prison they allow your family and friends to visit.
        At work you cannot even speak to your family and friends.

        In prison all expenses are paid by taxpayers with no work required.
        At work you get to pay all the expenses to go to work and then they
        deduct taxes from your salary to pay for prisoners.

        In prison you spend most of your life looking through the bars from
        the inside wanting to get out.
        At work you spend your time wanting to get out and inside bars.

        In prison you can join many programs which you can leave at any time.
        At work there are some programs you can never get out of.

        In prison there are wardens who are often sadistic.
        At work we have managers.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke118">
        A pastor went visiting one afternoon. He knocked on one door several
        times, but no one answered. He could see though the window that the
        television was on, so he took one of his cards, wrote "Revelations
        3:20" on it and stuck it in the door. (Revelations 3:20 says, "Behold,
        I stand at the door and knock; if anyone will open, I will come in.)

        The following Sunday, a woman handed him a card with her name and the
        following message: "Genesis 3:10". ("I heard thy voice and I was
        naked, so I hid myself.")

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke119">
        Officer Patrick McGuire of the New York City Police Department answers
        a call on his radio and reports to the scene of a car accident in the
        Queens-Midtown Tunnel. Officer McGuire notes that a new Buick had its
        front end merged with the rear end of a Chrysler. The driver of the
        Buick was Father Francis O'Boyle; the driver of the Chrysler was Rabbi
        Isaac Goldstein.

        After Officer McGuire verifies that Rabbi Goldstein has suffered no
        physical injuries in the accident, he walks back to survey the
        damages to each vehicle. Then, Officer McGuire walks over to Father
        O'Boyle and asks him: "Tell me, Father, just how fast was that Rabbi
        going when he backed into you?"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke120">
        A man was in his bed dying, slipping in and out of consciousness, and
        his wife came into the room with his doctor and the parish priest.
        "Mrs. Kelleher, you realize that the bill for my services is $1000,"
        the doctor said.

        "Fine, I'll see to it that it's paid from the insurance."

        "And, don't forget, Doreen, the funeral and casket will cost $1000,"
        the priest said.

        "Don't worry, Father, I'll see to it that you're paid as well."

        The three walked over to the bed and the doctor stood on one side of
        the man and the priest stood on the other. He opened his eyes and saw
        the two men there, and said, "Father, would you tell the people at my
        funeral that I died as Jesus died?"

        "Do you mean pure of heart and poor in spirit, Tom?"

        "No, I mean between two thieves."

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke121">
        A Jew, a Christian and a Muslim were having a discussion about who was
        the most religious.

        "I was riding my camel in the middle of the Sahara," exclaimed the
        Muslim. "Suddenly a fierce sandstorm appeared from nowhere. I truly
        thought my end had come as I lay next to my camel while we being buried
        deeper and deeper under the sand. But I did not lose my faith in the
        Almighty Allah, I prayed and prayed and suddenly, for a hundred meters
        all around me, the storm had stopped. Since that day I am a devout
        Muslim and am now learning to recite the Quran by memory."

        "One day while fishing," started the Christian, "I was in my little
        dinghy in the middle of the ocean. Suddenly a fierce storm appeared
        from nowhere. I truly thought my end had come as my little dinghy was
        tossed up and down in the rough ocean. But I did not lose my faith in
        Jesus Christ, I prayed and prayed and suddenly, for 300 meters all
        around me, the storm had stopped. Since that day I am a devout
        Christian and am now teaching young children about Him."

        "One day I was walking down the road," explained the Jew, "I was in
        my most expensive designer outfit in the middle of New York city.
        Suddenly I saw a black bag on the ground in front of me appear from
        nowhere. I put my hand inside and found a million dollars in cash.
        I truly thought my end had come as it was a Saturday and we are not
        allowed to handle money on Saturdays. But I did not lose my faith in
        Jehovah, I prayed and prayed and suddenly, for 500 meters all around
        me, it was Tuesday..."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke122">

        The MacTavish brothers decided that one of their number would
        go to America and make his fortune, coming back to share with
        the rest of them. The youngest, Ian, was chosen for this task.
        off he went, and he worked hard in America, and earned himself
        the usual fortune over a few years, and wired his brothers that
        he'd be returning with it.

        When he came back to the homeland (or hameland, as they'd call it)
        he got off the boat, and looked around for his brothers, but could
        not see anyone who looked familiar. Finally, a group of bearded
        strangers approached.

        "Ho, Ian, are ye not knowing yer own brothers?" asked the first
        one. Then Ian realized his brothers had grown beards.

        "Fer heaven's sake, laddies, what would ye be growin' them beards
        for, now?" he asked.

        "We had to, lad, ye took the razor wi' ye!"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke123">
        Johnny wanted to look suave for the local dance so he slipped into
        Taffy Lloys's barber shop. "I want a Tony Curtis haircut."

        So Taffy started trimming around the back with the clippers. Then he
        started going higher and higher with them till Johnny started to get a
        bit worried. But like most barbers, this one had verbal diarrhea, and
        was yapping non stop about movies and movie stars.

        "Yeah, I like Tony Curtis too." as he trimmed up and over Johnny's
        ears. "Wasn't he great in 'The King and I'?"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke124">
        William Lyon Phelps, the late Yale professor and popular lecturer,
        once said that he got credit for only one-forth of the after-dinner
        speeches he made.

        "Everytime i accept an invitation to speak, I really make four
        addresses. First, is the speech I prepare in advance. That is pretty
        good. Second is the speech I really make. Third is the speech I make
        on my way home, which is the best of all; and fourth is the speech the
        newspapers the next morning say I made, which bears no relation to any
        of the others.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke125">
        A straight line is the shortest distance between a baby and anything
        breakable.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke126">
        One night, a Delta twin-engine puddle jumper was flying somewhere
        above New Jersey. There were five people on board: the pilot, Michael
        Jordan, Bill Gates, the Dali Lama, and a hippie. Suddenly, an illegal
        oxygen generator exploded loudly in the luggage compartment, and the
        passenger cabin began to fill with smoke. The cockpit door opened,
        and the pilot burst into the compartment.

        "Gentlemen," he began, "I have good news and bad news. The bad news
        is that we're about to crash in New Jersey. The good news is that
        there are four parachutes, and I have one of them!" With that, the
        pilot threw open the door and jumped from the plane.

        Michael Jordan was on his feet in a flash. "Gentlemen," he said, "I
        am the world's greatest athlete. The world needs great athletes. I
        think the world's greatest athlete should have a parachute!" With
        these words, he grabbed one of the remaining parachutes, and hurtled
        through the door and into the night.

        Bill Gates rose and said, "Gentlemen, I am the world's smartest man.
        The world needs smart men. I think the world's smartest man should
        have a parachute, too." He grabbed one, and out he jumped.

        The Dali Lama and the hippie looked at one another. Finally, the Dali
        Lama spoke. "My son," he said, "I have lived a satisfying life and
        have known the bliss of True Enlightenment. You have your life ahead
        of you; you take a parachute, and I will go down with the plane."

        The hippie smiled slowly and said, "Hey, don't worry, pop. The
        world's smartest man just jumped out wearing my backpack."

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke127">
        An interoffice softball game was held every year between the marketing
        and support staff of one company. The support staff whipped the
        marketing department soundly.

        To show just *how* the marketing department earns their keep, they
        posted this memo on the bulletin board after the game:

        "The Marketing Department is pleased to announce that for the 1996
        Softball Season, we came in 2nd place, having lost but one game all
        year. The Support Department, however, had a rather dismal season,
        as they won only one game."

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke128">
        A man was boasting to his friend, "You know, I am a well known
        collector of antiques."

        His friend replied," Yes I know, I have seen your wife."

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke129">
        Dad: Son, what do you want for your birthday?

        Son: Just a radio, dad, with a sports car around it.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke130">
        The girl asked her lover, "Darling, if we get engaged will you give me
        a ring?"

        "Sure, " replied her lover "What's your phone number?"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke131">
        Young Man: Would you like to dance with me?

        Young Woman: Do you expect me to dance with a baby!

        Young Man: I'm so sorry. I didn't know you were pregnant.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke132">
        A doctor sent a bill to his patient. Underneath the bill he wrote:

        " This bill is now one year old."

        Back came the reply: "Happy Birthday!"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke133">
        On the day before the Battle of Hastings, King Harold said to his army
        commander, "Are the troops ready?"

        "They are, your Majesty", said the commander, "Would you like a
        demonstration?"

        "Yes, I would", said the King. So the commander lined all the archers
        up and instructed them to fire off a volley. Three thousand arrows
        sped through the air and landed a quarter of a mile away. But one
        clumsey archer fired straight up into the air, and the arrow went up
        several hundred feet, turned round and came back down again, landing
        about six inches from where the King was standing.

        "You want to watch that fellow", said the King. "If he's not careful,
        he'll have somebody's eye out tomorrow!"

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke134">
        What happend when women stood up for their rights? They lost their
        seats on the bus..........

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke135">
        Why is a pig's tail rather like having to get up at three AM??

        It's twirly.......

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke136">
        Three blondes are attempting to change a light bulb. One of
        them decides to call 911:

        Blonde: We need help. We're three blondes changing
        a light bulb.
        Operator: Hmmmmm. You put in a fresh bulb?
        Blonde: Yes.
        Operator: The power in the house in on?
        Blonde: Of course.
        Operator: And the switch is on?
        Blonde: Yes, yes.
        Operator: And the bulb still won't light up?
        Blonde: No, it's working fine.
        Operator: Then what's the problem?
        Blonde: We got dizzy spinning the ladder around and
        we all fell and hurt ourselves.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke137">
        When most people see a glass partially filled with water, they see it
        as either half full or half empty.

        Bob Dole sees it as a great place to put his teeth.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke138">
        Did you hear that at Bill Clinton's 50th birthday party, his cake was
        made in the shape of the USA embroidered with the 50 states?

        It was similar to the one Bob Dole had on his 50th birthday party
        which was embroidered with the 13 colonies!

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke139">
        President Clinton recently turned 50.

        It was noted as the first time he's met Bob Dole half-way on anything.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke140">
        If Bob Dole, Bill Clinton, and Pat Buchanan were in a boat and it
        tipped over, who would be saved?

        The United States.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke141">
        Ever notice that people who say they want to tell you something for
        your own good very seldom have anything good to say?

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke142">
        >From the Washington Post:

        What's with the people who put carpeting on the lid of their toilet
        seat? What are they thinking -- "Gosh, if we have a party there may
        not be enough standing room; I'd better carpet the toilet too."

        Have you ever noticed that the waiter who takes your order is not the
        one who brings your food anymore? What is THAT about? And which
        waiter are you tipping, anyway? I think next time I go to a
        restaurant I'll just say, "Oh, sorry, I only eat the food. The guy
        who pays the bill will be along shortly."

        Would somebody please explain to me those signs that say, "No animals
        allowed except for Seeing Eye Dogs?" Who is that sign for? Is it for
        the dog, or the blind person?

        Why do people give each other flowers? To celebrate various
        important occasions, they're killing living creatures? Why restrict
        it to plants? "Sweetheart, let's make up. Have this deceased squirrel"

        Can't we just get rid of wine lists? Do we really have to be reminded
        every time we go out to a nice restaurant that we have no idea what we
        are doing?

        Why don't they just give us a trigonometry quiz with the menu?

        If airline seat cushions are such great flotation devices, why don't
        you ever see anyone take one to the beach?

        Why do they call it a "building"? It looks like they're finished. Why
        isn't it a "built"?

        Why is it when you turn on the TV you see ads for telephone companies,
        and when you turn on the radio you hear ads for TV shows, and when you
        get put on hold on the phone you hear a radio station?

        Why is it illegal to park in a handicapped parking space but okay to
        go the bathroom in a handicapped stall?

        How come you have to pay someone to rotate your tires? Isn't that the
        basic idea behind the wheel? Don't they rotate on their own?

        All the king's HORSES and all the king's men? Are you kidding me? No
        wonder they couldn't put Humpty together again. Just what did those
        idiots expect the horses to do, anyway?

        Did you ever notice, when you are sitting at a red light, that when
        the person in front of you pulls up a couple of inches, you are
        compelled to move up too? Do we really think we are making progress
        toward our destination? "Whew, I thought we would be late, but now
        that I am nine inches closer, I can stop for coffee and a danish!"

        Isn't it weird that we drink milk, stuff designed to nourish baby
        cows? How did THAT happen? Did some cattleman once say, "Oh, man,
        I can't wait till them calves are done so I can get ME a hit of that
        stuff."

        Have you ever noticed how they keep improving your laundry detergent,
        but they still can't get those blue flakes out? Why do we trust them
        to get our clothes clean? These guys can't even get the DETERGENT
        white!

        Did you see these new minivan ads? All they talk about are cup
        holders, kiddie seats and doors. What kind of advertising is that?
        When you see an ad for a suit, do they say, "And look at the zipper!
        Carefully hidden, but easily accessible when you need it!" I think
        not.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke143">
        A priest and a rabbi operated a church and a synagogue across the
        street from each other. Since their schedules intertwined, they
        decided to go in together to buy a car. After the purchase, they drove
        it home and parked in on the street between their establishments.

        A few minutes later, the rabbi looked out and saw the priest
        sprinkling water on their new car. It didn't need a wash, so he ran
        out and asked the priest what he was doing. "I'm blessing it," the
        priest replied.

        The rabbi considered this a moment, then said, "Oh," and ran back
        inside the synagogue. He reappeared a moment later with a hacksaw,
        ran to the back of the car and cut off the last two inches of the
        tailpipe.

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke144">
        Vincent Van Gogh had a real large family. Here's a listing of some of
        his lesser known relatives.

        The grandfather who moved to Yugoslavia ........ U.Gogh

        The brother who accidentally bleached all his clothes white - Hue Gogh

        The sister who wore a mini skirt and liked to dance in bars...Go Gogh

        The real obnoxious brother ......................Please Gogh

        The brother who ate prunes .......................Gotta Gogh

        The uncle who worked at a convenience store .....Stop N Gogh

        His dizzy aunt ...................................Verti Gogh

        The cousin who moved to Illinois .................Chica Gogh

        His magician uncle...........................Wherediddy Gogh

        The cousin who lived in Mexico ....................Amee Gogh

        Another cousin who lived in Mexico ................Grin Gogh

        Nephew that drove a stage coach...............Wells Far Gogh

        Uncle who was constipated......................... Cant Gogh

        Aunt who was a good dancer......................... Tan Gogh

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke145">
        Andy went to Mexico where the weather was more predictable than
        Seattle.................

        Chili today, hot-tamale.....................

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke146">
        The Bride and Groom sat up all night waiting for their sexual
        relations to arrive........

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke147">
        Silence isn't always golden, sometimes it's guilt!

    </entry>
    <entry key="joke148">
        The Policeman had stopped the man for obvious drunken driving, but
        since the guy had a clean record, made him park the car and took him
        home in the patrol car. "Are you sure this is your house?" the cop
        asked as they drove into a rather fashionable neighborhood.

        "Shertainly." said the drunk, "and if you'll just open the door f'me,
        I can prove it to ya." Entering the living room, he said " You shee
        that piano ? Thash mine. You shee that giant television set ? Thast
        mine too. Now follow me."

        The police officer followed the man as he shakily negotiated the
        stairs to the second floor. The drunk pushed open the first door they
        came to. "Thish ish my bedroom," he announced. "Shee the bed there ?
        Thast mine! Shee that woman lying in the bed ? Thash my wife. An' see
        that guy lying next to her ?

        "Yeah ?" the cop replied suspiciously. Beginning at this point to
        seriously doubt the man's story.

        "Well, thash me !"

    </entry>

    <entry key="joke149">
        The hospital patient, annoyed by the lack of attention he received
        after returning to his hospital room from the intensive-care unit,
        exclaimed, "I've gone from I.C.U. to 'no see you'!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke150">

        Two roaches were munching on garbage in an alley. "I was in that
        new restaurant across the street," said one. "It's so clean! The
        kitchen is spotless, the floors are gleaming white. It's so
        sanitary the whole place shines." "Please," said the other roach,
        frowning. "Not while I'm eating!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke151">

        An infant rabbit was orphaned. Fortunately though, a family of
        squirrels took it in and raised it as if it were one of their own.
        This adoption led to some peculiar behaviors on the part of the
        rabbit, including a tendency for it to eschew jumping but rather to
        embrace running around like its step-siblings.

        As the rabbit passed through puberty, however, it soon faced an
        identity crisis (don't we all!). It went to its step-parents to
        discuss the problem. It allowed as to how it felt different from
        its step-siblings, was unsure of its place in the universe, and was
        generally forlorn. Their response was,

        "Don't scurry, be hoppy."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke152">

        There once was a 94 year old nun whose wornout body began to
        surrender. Her doctor prescribed for her a shot of whiskey three
        times a day, to relax her tenseness. However, not to be lured into
        worldly pleasures, she huffily declined. But her mother superior
        knew the elderly sister loved milk. So she instructed the kitchen
        to spike the milk three times a day.

        Eventually, the elderly pious one approached her final hour. As the
        several sisters gathered around her at bedside, the mother superior
        asked if she wanted to leave them any words of wisdom... "Oh, yes,"
        she replied.

        "Never sell that cow!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke153">

        THE BOSS'S BASIC RULES

        Rule 1: The Boss is always right!

        Rule 2: In the impossible hypothesis that a subordinate may be right,
        becomes immediately operative.

        Rule 3: The boss does not sleep; he rests.

        Rule 4: The Boss is never late; he is delayed elsewhere.

        Rule 5: The Boss never leaves his work; his attention is required
        elsewhere.

        Rule 6: The Boss never reads the paper in his office; he studies.

        Rule 7: The Boss is always chief, even in his bathing togs.

        Rule 8: Whomsoever may enter the boss's office with an idea of his
        own must leave the office with the boss's ideas.

        Rule 9: If, in your lamentable ignorance, you fail to grasp the
        truth, fear not; return to rule 1.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke154">

        A Chinese scholar was lecturing when all the lights in the
        auditorium went out.

        He asked members of the audience to raise their hands. As
        soon as they had all complied, the lights went on again. He then
        said, "Prove wisdom of Old Chinese saying: 'Many hands make light
        work.'"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke155">

        Cartoon:

        Man stands in his doorway in full fishing gear. Man stands opposite
        in business attire.

        Man 2: I know you're in bed with the flu, John, but I need the key
        to the file cabinet.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke156">

        i just read about two people who were driving their car around some
        town in New Jersey. They had a stick of dynamite with them.

        Well, one of them wondered what would happen if they lit the
        dynamite and threw it out the window at 3 am. So they lit it up and
        tossed it.

        Only the window was rolled up.

        They were both taken to the hospital, where they underwent surgery.

        I think they're recovering, but they have been disinvited to the
        next Mensa meeting...
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke157">


        Man relieves himself on dog: Sparks panic

        Rio De Janeiro, Brazil - A Rio neighbourhood went to the dogs and
        echoed with the sound of gunfire after a man and a terrier got into
        a dispute over a call of nature.

        The toilet shootout developed when a beer-filled Brazillian student
        went to relieve himself against a tree, Brazilian news agency Estado
        reported.

        The student mistakenly urinated on a pit bull terrier that was
        watering the same vegetation and as a result ended up brawling with
        the dog's owner, Estado said.

        When the student's friends chased the owner and his dog to a service
        station, security guards, thinking a robbery was in progress, fired shots
        into the air, bringing police rushing to the scene.

        After a brief spell behind bars, however, the two men were reported
        to have made up -- over a beer.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke158">

        There was a kid who excelled at school in all subects except math.
        In desperation his agnostic parents sent him to a Catholic parochial
        school to see if the nuns could straighten him out.

        The kid immediately buckled down. Every night he went to his room,
        closed the door, and studied his math. When report cards came out he
        had A's in everything and an A+ in math.

        When his parents asked him what made the difference, he replied, "I
        knew they meant business the first time I walked into the school.
        Right inside the front door they've got a big statue of a guy nailed
        to a plus sign."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke159">

        Marketing Buzz Words Translated:

        * NEW - Different color from previous design
        * ALL NEW - Parts not interchangable with previous
        design
        * EXCLUSIVE - Imported product
        * UNMATCHED - Almost as good as the competition
        * DESIGNED SIMPLICITY - Manufacturer's cost cut to the bone
        * FOOLPROOF OPERATION - No provision for adjustments
        * ADVANCED DESIGN - The advertising agency doesn't understand it
        * IT'S HERE AT LAST! - Rush job; Nobody knew it was coming
        * FIELD-TESTED - Manufacturer lacks test equipment
        * HIGH ACCURACY - Unit on which all parts fit
        * DIRECT SALES ONLY - Factory had big argument with distributor
        * YEARS OF DEVELOPMENT - We finally got one that works
        * REVOLUTIONARY - It's different from our competitiors
        * BREAKTHROUGH - We finally figured out a way to sell it
        * FUTURISTIC - No other reason why it looks the way it does
        * DISTINCTIVE - A different shape and color than the others
        * MAINTENANCE-FREE - Impossible to fix
        * RE-DESIGNED - Previous faults corrected, we hope..
        * HAND-CRAFTED - Assembly machines operated without gloves on
        * PERFORMANCE PROVEN - Will operate through the warranty period
        * MEETS ALL STANDARDS - Ours, not yours
        * ALL SOLID-STATE - Heavy as Bill Clinton with Roseanne on his
        lap!
        * BROADCAST QUALITY - Gives a picture and produces noise
        * HIGH RELIABILITY - We made it work long enough to ship it
        * SMPTE BUS COMPATABILE- When completed, will be shipped by Greyhound
        * NEW GENERATION - Old design failed, mabey this one will work
        * MIL-SPEC COMPONENTS - We got a good deal at a government auction
        * CUSTOMER SERVICE
        ACROSS THE COUNTRY - You can return it from most airports
        * UNPRECEDENTED
        PERFORMANCE - Nothing we ever had before worked THIS way
        * BUILT TO PRECISION
        TOLERANCES - We finally got it to fit together
        * SATISFACTION
        GUARANTEED - Manufacturer's, upon cashing your check
        * MICROPROCESSOR
        CONTROLLED - Does things we can't explain
        * AEROSPACE TECHNOLOGY - One of our techs was laid off by Boeing
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke160">

        Paddy & Murphy are walking through this wood, when they see a sign
        saying 'tree fellers wanted'. Paddy turns to murphy, says 'Ah, 'Tis a
        shame there's only two of us!'
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke161">

        Moishe had started in the second-hand trade but was now one of the
        richest businessmen in London. As his Rolls Royce stopped in front of
        the Ritz one night an old school chum, who had fallen on hard times,
        was waiting for him.

        "Hey Moishe, remember me?"

        "Eddie Rozenbloom, of course I do. haven't seen you in years. How's
        business?"

        "Moishe," says Eddie, "I've hit a bad patch. Infact I was wondering
        if you could let me have ten pounds for a bed."

        "Sure Eddie. Bring it round in the morning!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke162">

        Did you hear about the prawn that went to a disco and pulled a
        muscle?
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke163">

        GEORGE: What instructions did Noah give his sons about fishing off
        the ark?
        BILL : I don't know.
        GEORGE: Go easy on the bait, boys. I only have two worms.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke164">

        The difference between politics and baseball is that in baseball when
        you get caught stealing, you're out.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke165">

        Talking to an American lady during a lengthy delay a little while
        ago

        ME: Have you been on holiday?
        AL: Yeah.
        ME: What did you think of England?
        AL: I loved it, but why are your traffic signals so noisy?
        ME: ???
        AL: Well, they go beep beep beep.
        ME: Oh, that's so that blind people know when to cross.
        AL: Oh reeally?? In the States we don't let 'em drive.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke166">

        She used to be married to a trapeze artist, but she caught him in
        the act........
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke167">

        Three Strings wanted to drink some beer so they went to Mr. Rope's
        carry-out. The first String says, "I'll show you how to buy beer,"
        and goes in. "I'd like a six-pack of beer, please." Mr. Rope says,
        "You're one of those Strings. We don't serve your kind here. Get
        out of here!"

        So the second String says, "Watch me," and goes in. In his deepest
        voice, he says, "I'd like a six-pack of beer, please." Mr. Rope
        says, "You're another one of those Strings. Get out of here!"

        The third String says, "I'll show you how it's done." He curls
        himself into a clove-hitch, unravels his head, goes into the
        carry-out, and says, "I'd like a six-pack of beer, please." Mr. Rope
        asks, "Aren't you one of those Strings?"

        He says, "I'm a FRAYED KNOT!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke168">

        So Paddy and Murphy are in a wild west bar trying to scrounge a pint
        off the bartender. They've been at it for about an hour when in
        walks this guy with a head under his arm. The bartender jumps up and
        gives the guy a sack of gold. Paddy and Murphy are way confused. The
        bartender explains. "I hate the Indians ya' see!" he says "I hates
        'em so much I'll give a sack of gold to anyone who brings me an
        Indian's head..."

        So off Paddy and Murphy go, equipped with rifle, saw, hammer etc.

        After a while they find a lone Indian, and they shoot him off a cliff
        and down into a ravine. Down go Paddy and Murphy, after him. At the
        bottom Paddy starts cutting off the Indian's head while Murphy
        stands watch.

        After a couple of minute Murphy taps Paddy on the shoulder, says
        "Paddy, I think you ought to look at this." Paddy ignores him...
        "No, Paddy, I'm serious, you really ought to take a look!!"

        Paddy lops off the Indian's head and looks up where Murphy's
        pointing. On either side of the ravine there's like, a million
        Indians, war paint and the lot. Paddy looks at Murphy with a glint
        in his eye and says "Well, I'll be, mate! We're gonna be
        millionaires!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke169">

        The Number You Have Reached.....
        Hello, you have reached the office of the New York Board of Rabbis.
        Our Rabbi is ready to answer any of your questions.
        If you are Orthodox, press 6, 1, 3.
        If you are Conservative, press 1 or 2.
        If you are Reform, press any button you like.
        If you are Reconstructionist, press all the buttons.
        If you are Lubavitch, please wait a moment for the Moshiach to answer.
        (Beep)

        Hello, you have reached the Orthodox Rabbi.
        The answer to your question is that it is absolutely forbidden by the
        Torah. If you wish to change your affiliation, press 1, 8.
        (Beep)

        Hello, you have reached the Conservative Rabbi.
        The answer to your question is that we have ruled that either answer
        is acceptable to some of us and neither answer is acceptable to all
        of us. We hope that this has been helpful.
        If you wish to change your affiliation, press 1, 8.
        (Beep)

        Hello, you have reached the Reform Rabbi.
        The answer to your question is: If you want to, sure! Why not? Who are
        we to say?
        However, if you wish to change your affiliation, press 1, 8.
        (Beep)

        Hello, you have reached the Reconstructionist Rabbi.
        The answer to your question presumes that there is an answer. We have
        not decided that issue yet. However, my role is to empower you to
        answer your own question. To answer your own question now, please hang
        up....if you are still there.
        (Click)
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke170">

        Two crayfish were in the restaurant's aquarium. It seemed this would
        be their last night together, so the male crayfish whispered sweet
        nothings in her ear.

        She said, "Okay, but will you still respect me in the mornay?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke171">

        *A Chrysanthemum by any other name would be easier to spell.........
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke172">

        I don't want to say she was fat, but she had more chins than the
        Singapore phone book...............
    </entry>

    <entry key="joke173">
        A husband and wife are driving and they get pulled over by a
        policeman. The policeman gets to the car and asks for the man's
        license.

        The man replies,"Why do you need my license? What did I do wrong?"

        The policeman answers,"You were traveling 45 mph in a 30 mph zone."

        "Come on, officer," the man replies,"You know I was only going 35."

        "No you weren't!" quips the wife,"I told you you were speeding! I
        told you not to go fast. I knew you'd get a ticket!"

        "Shut Up!" grunts the husband.

        The policeman continues,"I'm also am charging you for going through
        a red light."

        "Officer," the man explains, "you know as well as I, that light was
        yellow - not red."

        The wife pipes in,"No, it was most definitely red - I told you it
        was red - I told you."

        At this point the husband is infuriated. He yells at his wife,
        "SHUT UP!"

        The policeman exclaims,"Hey! stop yelling at your wife!" He then
        turns to the wife and asks,"Does he always talk to you this way?"

        She calmly replies,"No, only when he's been drinking."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke174">

        Cat on a walk forces thief to turn tail
        --------------------------------------

        Sometime in january this year....

        Moscow -- A thief who fancied an attractive fur hat on the head of a
        passer-by got more than he bargained for when he tried to snatch it.

        The fur collar of the victim's coat turned out to be a Siamese cat,
        which sunk its jaws and claws into the thief, who quickly turned
        tail, the local paper Vologodskiy Novosti (quite a mouthful, eh?;) )
        said in Vologda in north-east Russia.

        "There is no animal more frightening than a cat, especially on it's
        master's shoulders," the paper noted.

        The cat's owner had taken his pet on his walk as added protection
        against the freezing weather.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke175">

        Lioness catches youth with pants down
        *************************************

        Maracaibo, Venezuela - A lioness attacked and mauled a Venezuelan
        youth who had hopped into her pen to answer a call of nature.

        "I had my trousers around my knees when I heard some growling and
        saw this ferocious animal hurling itself on top of me," the 19-year
        -old man said from his hospital bed in this western Venezualan city.

        He wrestled tarzan-style with the lioness , which sank its claws and
        teeth into his head and torso "while I just tried to get if off me so
        I could pull up my trousers."

        But he escaped to tell the tale when a quick-thinking friend used a
        brick to knock out the lioness.

        The youth was badly wounded,but well enough to tell a local newspaper
        how the attack affected his diarrhea.

        "It disappeared as if by magic!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke176">

        An elephant met a lion in the jungle and asked, "Why do you make such
        a fool of yourself by roaring so much?"

        "Oh, there's a good reason for it," replied the lion jovially. "They
        call me the king of the beasts because I advertise."

        A rabbit, hiding in the brush, overheard this conversation and was
        deeply impreseed. He thought he would try the lion's strategy and when
        he encountered a fox tried to roar like the lion -- but it came out a
        tiny sqeak. The unimpressed fox had himself a meal in the woods,
        reminding himself in the process that it does not pay to advertise
        unless you have the goods.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke177">

        Kidding Secretary of Labour Arthur Goldberg,in a speech before an
        AFL-CIO convention, President Kennedy told how Goldberg got lost while
        mountain climbing in the Alps. Search parties were sent out to find
        him. The Red Cross finally joined the rescue attempt, and their men
        went around calling out,"Goldberg! Goldberg! It's the Red Cross."
        Finally from the mountains came a voice: "I gave at the office!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke178">

        A man went in to his doctor complaining that he was short sighted. The
        doctor took him outside and pointed to the sky, "what can you see"
        asked the doctor, " the sun" replied the man. "Well how far do you
        want to see" the doctor replies....
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke179">

        What's the difference between a well dressed man and a tired dog?
        One wears a suit, and the other just pants.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke180">

        Never give up because life gets harder as you get older. After
        preschool the road of life keeps getting bumpier and bumpier and
        bumpier. -- Angela Martin, age 11

        Never blow in a cat's ear because if you do, usually after three or
        four times, they will bite your lips! And they don't let go for at
        least a minute. -- Lisa Coburn, age 9

        Don't think life is easy, because when you get older it is hard work.
        I used to think life was easy, now I have to do the dishes every
        other day. -- Nick Coleman, age 9

        Take risks. I mean, if you like this person and you don't know if
        they like you, ask them out and see what happens. I liked this girl
        and I asked her out. She said no and she hates me now, but I took
        that risk. -- Bruce Wagner, age 13

        A realist is more correct about things in life than an optimist. But
        the optimist seems to have more friends and much more fun. -- Megan,
        age 14
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke181">

        The beguiling ideas about science quoted here were gleaned from
        essays, exams, and classroom discussions. Most were from 5th and 6th
        graders. They illustrate Mark Twain's contention that the "most
        interesting information comes from children, for they tell all they
        know and then stop."

        Question: What is one horsepower? Answer: One horsepower is the
        amount of energy it takes to drag a horse 500 feet in one second.

        You can listen to thunder after lightening and tell how close you
        came to getting hit. If you don't hear it you got hit, so never mind.

        Talc is found on rocks and on babies.

        The law of gravity says no fair jumping up without coming back down.

        When they broke open molecules, they found they were only stuffed
        with atoms. But when they broke open atoms, they found them stuffed
        with explosions.

        When people run around and around in circles we say they are crazy.
        When planets do it we say they are orbiting.

        Rainbows are just to look at, not to really understand.

        Someday we may discover how to make magnets that can point in any
        direction.

        South America has cold summers and hot winters, but somehow they
        still manage.

        Most books now say our sun is a star. But it still knows how to change
        back into a sun in the daytime.

        Water freezes at 32 degrees and boils at 212 degrees. There are 180
        degrees between freezing and boiling because there are 180 degrees
        between north and south.

        A vibration is a motion that cannot make up its mind which way it
        wants to go.

        There are 26 vitamins in all, but some of the letters are yet to be
        discovered. Finding them all means living forever.

        There is a tremendous weight pushing down on the center of the Earth
        because of so much population stomping around up here these days.

        Lime is a green-tasting rock.

        Many dead animals in the past changed to fossils while others
        preferred to be oil.

        Genetics explain why you look like your father and if you don't why
        you should.

        Vacuums are nothings. We only mention them to let them know we know
        they're there.

        Some oxygen molecules help fires burn while others help make water,
        so sometimes it's brother against brother.

        Some people can tell what time it is by looking at the sun. But I
        have never been able to make out the numbers.

        We say the cause of perfume disappearing is evaporation. Evaporation
        gets blamed for a lot of things people forget to put the top on.

        To most people solutions mean finding the answers. But to chemists
        solutions are things that are still all mixed up.

        In looking at a drop of water under a microscope, we find there are
        twice as many H's as O's.

        Clouds are high flying fogs.

        I am not sure how clouds get formed. But the clouds know how to do
        it, and that is the important thing.

        Clouds just keep circling the earth around and around. And around.
        There is not much else to do.

        Cyanide is so poisonous that one drop of it on a dogs tongue will
        kill the strongest man.

        A blizzard is when it snows sideways.

        A monsoon is a French gentleman.

        Thunder is a rich source of loudness.

        Isotherms and isobars are even more important than their names sound.

        It is so hot in some places that the people there have to live in
        other places.

        The wind is like the air, only pushier.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke182">

        Three men, an Italian, a Jew, and a Pole, are sentenced to spend 15
        years in solitary confinement. The judge, feeling sorry for the men,
        decides to allow each to take with him whatever he wants.

        The Italian says, "I'd like to take a woman with me." The judge
        reluctantly agrees, and the Italian takes his wife and heads off to
        solitary. The Jew says, "I'd like to take a telephone with me." The
        judge agrees, and off goes the Jew with his telephone. The Pole pulls
        out a hand-held calculator and furiously punches the buttons for a few
        minutes. He then announces, "I'd like to take 3,000 cartons of
        cigarettes with me." The judge agrees, and off goes the Pole with his
        cigarettes.

        After 15 years they open the Italian's cell, and out comes the Italian
        with his wife and 15 children: "It wasn't so bad...." The Jew emerges
        and announces he is now a multimillionaire, having set up a successful
        business by telephone.

        The Pole then comes out, trembling like a leaf, and says, "Anybody got
        a match?"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke183">

        The reason lightning doesn't strike twice in the same place is that
        the same place isn't there the second time.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke184">

        St. Peter went to work one day to find 2 lines of men at The Gate.
        One line snaked its way across heaven, as far as St. Pete could see.
        Above that line hung a sign reading:

        This Line Is For Men Whose Wives
        *ALWAYS* Told Them What To Do

        In the other line, he noticed only one man standing under a sign that
        read:

        This Line Is For Men Whose Wives
        *NEVER* Told Them What To Do

        St. Peter asked the man, "What are you doing in this line?"

        To which the man meekly replied, "My wife told me to stand here!"
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke185">

        Fashion is something that goes in one era and out the other......
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke186">

        My mother in law called today...

        I knew it was her, when she knocked on the front door all the mice
        threw themselves on the traps!
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke187">

        Young Jock MacTavish got down on his knees to propose to her when a
        10p piece dropped out of his pocket and rolled under the sofa. In the
        20 minutes it took him to find it she had lost interest.............
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke188">

        What would our classic situation comedies be like in the era of
        computers?

        Beverly Hillbillies-

        Miss Jane tries to convince Mr. Drysdale to network all the PCs in the
        bank, but, typically, he won't spend the money. Frustrated, Miss Jane
        pleads with Jed Clampett to persuade Mr. Drysdale to "put in the LAN,"
        but Jed thinks she said "put in the ham." Jed then gets Granny to cook
        up a dozen hams and has Jethro and Ellie Mae bring them to the bank.
        When they arrive, everybody is out to lunch, so Jethro begins to
        distribute the hams, but is frustrated when he can't get the coaxial
        cable to stay attached to the ham bone. To further complicate matters,
        Ellie May has brought along her pet goats, which begin to eat the ham
        and cable, causing the the VAX to short out and force an emergency
        electronic fund transfer of the Clampett millions to a competitive
        bank. As Mr. Drysdale is seen chasing Miss Jane down the hall with a
        crazed look in his eye, swinging a ham at her, Jed is heard to remark,
        "Weee- doggie! Why look at that Granny. Mr. Drysdale is so happy about
        whut we done, he's gonna give Miss Jane her own ham!"


        The Mary Tyler Moore Show-

        Mr. Grant tells Mary to come up with some hard facts about all the
        activity out in Silicon Valley. Mary grabs her Mac portable and jumps
        on a plane west. Unfortunately, she leaves the Mac switched on and,
        due to an undiscovered bug in the latest release of System and Finder,
        the hard disk continually optimizes itself when no keyboard input is
        recorded for more than five minutes. Needless to say, she has a dead
        Mac when arriving and spends the next few hours trying to find a
        replacement. Meanwhile, Ted begins his broadcast and notes that "We
        expected to have some good information about Silicon Valley for this
        broadcast, but somebody had to take a Mac and not a reliable laptop
        PC!" Frantic, Mary calls long distance over crystalline fiber optic
        lines to get help from Rhoda, who doesn't answer the phone because she
        is playing Bomber and has the headphones on. However, Phyllis's snotty
        daughter is around and answers. She listens to Mary whine, then hangs
        up the phone. Mary is last seen violently flinging the Mac out a
        speeding taxi window while crossing the Bay Bridge.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke189">

        DALLAS (04-10) - Contributor: [shodai@pipeline.com] - Last week in
        Texas, the Legislature passed a law mandating that criminals provide
        at least 24 hour notice to their potential victims before they
        perpetrate their crime.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke190">

        IRS agent to errant taxpayer: "But that's just the point, sir. We
        DO plan to make a federal case out of it."
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke191">

        I went to the doctor, it was quite serious. He gave me 6 months to
        live. But then I couldn't pay his bill so he gave me another 6 months.
    </entry>
    <entry key="joke192">

        A brunette was walking down the middle of the street bobbing her head
        saying "88, 88, 88, 88." A blonde saw her and asked her why she did
        it. The brunette said it was fun and said she should try it. So they
        were both walking down the middle of the street saying "88, 88, 88"
        All of a sudden a huge semi-truck came along and the brunette jumped
        out of the way...

        A brunette was walking down the middle of the street bobbing her head
        saying "89, 89, 89".
    </entry>

</properties>